[Music]
[音乐]
本教程是关于这种类型的卡的
this tutorial is about this type of card
当您拉动标签时，我称为舞台布景
在每一侧它打开，您会得到一个
this tutorial is about this type of card
I call a stage set as you pull the tabs
3d Vista，所以这是一个使它成为
生日卡，那我就来一张
I call a stage set as you pull the tabs
on each side it opens up and you get a
这是作为圣诞贺卡制作的
选项卡在内部更简单，然后
on each side it opens up and you get a
3d Vista so this was one made it's a
我有一个我自己检查的
这一切如何运作，您只需拉一下标签
3d Vista so this was one made it's a
birthday card then I've got one here
它打开了两个主要部分
是框架，然后另一边是
birthday card then I've got one here
which was made as a Christmas card pull
真的，这是一条长条
双方的场景，然后
which was made as a Christmas card pull
the tabs bit more simple inside and then
您拉动测量的两个位是
有点复杂，因为碎片
the tabs bit more simple inside and then
I've got one I made myself just checking
你拉，因为他们进来像
他们需要成为那些人
I've got one I made myself just checking
how it all works is you pull the tabs
件必须是尺寸的一半
整个正面和两个墙头
how it all works is you pull the tabs
and it opens up its two main pieces one
这些位，因为它们填补了空白
他们需要是差距的一半
and it opens up its two main pieces one
is the frame and then the other side is
所以我已经提前做好了
所有的测量都标记在
is the frame and then the other side is
really one long strip this is the back
它，所以您可以看到它们是什么
主要的正面这是一半
really one long strip this is the back
of the scene the two sides and then the
a4卡的21厘米宽
高度是a4的一半
of the scene the two sides and then the
two bits that you pull the measuring is
重要的是这个窗口，所以
十厘米乘八厘米
two bits that you pull the measuring is
slightly complicated because the pieces
这是背面的一块
您正在寻找的房间
slightly complicated because the pieces
that you pull because they come in like
那是10 x 10，就像你看到的那样
它的宽度与
that you pull because they come in like
this they need to be each of those pulls
窗户，但比
整体
this they need to be each of those pulls
pieces has to be half the size of the
窗户，然后这是两个方面
会粘在一起的碎片，如果
pieces has to be half the size of the
whole frontage and the two wall bits
我们看看整个长片
两侧背面和两个位
whole frontage and the two wall bits
these bits because they fill in the gap
你拉，你会看到双方都有
这些插槽切入它们，然后
these bits because they fill in the gap
they need to be half the size of the gap
图像在穿过
插槽，这是我的几个酒吧
they need to be half the size of the gap
so I've made all the pieces in advance
剪掉这些是
贴在房间的后面，这样
so I've made all the pieces in advance
with all the measurements marked up on
这将是房间的后面
会像这样坚持下去
with all the measurements marked up on
it so you can see what they are this is
是整件的尺寸
跨21个，所以每个必须是十个
it so you can see what they are this is
the main frontage this is half a piece
半然后宽度
窗口是十，所以这些必须是一半
the main frontage this is half a piece
of a4 card the 21 centimetres across and
其中有五个，所以当
这样就可以了
of a4 card the 21 centimetres across and
the height is half a sheet of a4 the
酒吧有这些插槽
通过最靠近前面的那一个
the height is half a sheet of a4 the
important thing is this window so that's
将会是一个半的窗口
从底部和
important thing is this window so that's
ten centimetres by eight centimetres
它后面的一个将是两个半
厘米高，他们都是两个
ten centimetres by eight centimetres
this is the piece that goes at the back
厘米深，它们是一个又一个
距离边缘半厘米
this is the piece that goes at the back
of the room that you're looking into so
他们去了其中两个
一个在背面的每一侧，所以我现在
of the room that you're looking into so
that's 10 by 10 as you can see it's a
只是把这些粘在一起，我会保持
在您打开时测量
that's 10 by 10 as you can see it's a
little bit it's the same width as the
整个卡片你不会看到所有的
测量我有一个房间，所以
little bit it's the same width as the
window but it's a little bit higher than
就像那样，我会坚持
这些一起让我们放一些胶水
window but it's a little bit higher than
the whole
这个标签在这里我已经预先评分了
然后将其折叠并弄皱，就这样
the whole
window and then these are the two side
会很好地移动，但是当你
真正让自己不要忘记
window and then these are the two side
pieces that are going to glue on so if
真正压制所有折痕，所以它们
他们移动得非常好，这样就可以了
pieces that are going to glue on so if
we look at how this whole long piece the
像这样的权利，所以一侧坚持
现在我要坚持另一面
we look at how this whole long piece the
two sides the back and the two bits that
到另一边才能做到这一点
长条，所以放在那里
two sides the back and the two bits that
you pull you'll see that the sides have
标签在房间的后面
正如我所说的，把胶水放在这里
you pull you'll see that the sides have
these slots cut in them and then the
始终粘合时使其光滑
将胶水涂抹到折痕上，这样
these slots cut in them and then the
images are on bars that go through the
在那里
好圆，使它顺利进行
images are on bars that go through the
slots here's a couple of bars that I've
所以这就是长片的样子
所以当它关闭时，它会像
slots here's a couple of bars that I've
cut out these are the sides that will
所以现在我们必须将其添加到
框架，我们有两个袖子
cut out these are the sides that will
stick on to the the back of the room so
所以我们有两个袖子
你可以在后面的碎片
stick on to the the back of the room so
this will be the back of the room these
看到我没有给他们上色，但是
这里有一个袖子这里有一个袖子
this will be the back of the room these
are going to stick on like this so these
他们是保持这些滑动的
零件就位，并使它们移动
are going to stick on like this so these
are the measurements the whole piece is
你想让他们移动的方式，所以我有
其中的两个只是一小部分
are the measurements the whole piece is
21 across so each of these has to be ten
长于整个高度
滑动片，所以它们是十点五
21 across so each of these has to be ten
and a half and then the width of the
厘米，它们将粘在上面
这个的背面，所以我有
and a half and then the width of the
window is ten so these have to be half
此处的尺寸，但我会保留
我要去背面测量
window is ten so these have to be half
of that so these are five so when it's
坚持这些，他们就去
冲在我涂胶的窗户上
of that so these are five so when it's
in position it'll be like that and then
两个标签1 2和这些像这样
理想情况下，我会对其进行测量，以便
in position it'll be like that and then
it has these slots that the bars go
它们在上方完全等距
在窗框下面，所以有一个是
it has these slots that the bars go
through the one nearest the front of the
另一个，只是确保
褶皱也很好，但粘在那些上
through the one nearest the front of the
window that'll be one and a half
二
然后小心地粘上你
window that'll be one and a half
centimeters high from the bottom and the
真的不希望它损失太多，
粘上袖子就这样了
centimeters high from the bottom and the
one behind it will be two and a half
两个袖子齐平
窗口的边缘现在我们
one behind it will be two and a half
centimeters high they're both two
这一块，并通过所有
它会像这样，所以放一个
centimeters high they're both two
centimeters deep and they're one and a
穿过那边，另一边
通过那里，所以现在你可以看到它
centimeters deep and they're one and a
half centimeters in from the edges so
关闭这些将出现在
尽管我的测量是如此微小
half centimeters in from the edges so
there are two of these pieces they go
关闭，因为还有一点
缝隙，然后将其拉出
there are two of these pieces they go
one on each side of the back so now I'll
现在打开，我们将这些条放到位
所以条的长度是十点
one on each side of the back so now I'll
just stick these together I'll keep the
两个略长于
窗口的宽度和高度
just stick these together I'll keep the
measurements out of you so when you open
的酒吧是一分七
略小于高度
measurements out of you so when you open
the whole cards you won't see all the
插槽，每个酒吧都有这两个
每端都折叠的标签
the whole cards you won't see all the
measurements I've got that one room so
他们下来你不折他们，
给他们打分，你只要把它们折下来
measurements I've got that one room so
it's gonna be like that so I'll stick
他们会穿过他们的插槽，所以我会
像这样折下来然后喂
it's gonna be like that so I'll stick
these together let's put some glue on
他们通过插槽哦，是的
一旦通过插槽，您就可以
these together let's put some glue on
this tab here I've already pre scored it
再次拉直标签，然后在
摆弄对方
this tab here I've already pre scored it
and folded it and creased it so it's all
就在那儿，我们去那里的胖子吧
装进我犯了一个小错误
and folded it and creased it so it's all
going to move nicely but when you're
我把数字放在里面
显示，但不要担心，这是
going to move nicely but when you're
actually making your own don't forget to
另一对，所以现在您可以看到
像现在这样有两个酒吧
actually making your own don't forget to
really crimp all the creases so they
可以添加图像并将其粘贴到
如果您这样看，它们会在关闭时关闭
really crimp all the creases so they
they move really well so that's gonna go
您会看到插槽越来越近，
靠得更近，所以越靠近
they move really well so that's gonna go
like that right so stuck one side on and
酒吧是在舞台的前面
较小的图像必须是
like that right so stuck one side on and
now I'm going to stick the other side on
正面图片不得超过3个
厘米宽
now I'm going to stick the other side on
to the other side to make this really
所以我将其粘在
用空白面将其粘上
to the other side to make this really
long strip so to put there
因为那稍微更具美感
想要背面有胶水，因此图像
long strip so to put there
the tabs go behind the back of the room
只是站在那里而不是
在酒吧后面，您实际上可以将其粘上
the tabs go behind the back of the room
as I call it and put the glue on here
到酒吧的任何地方
关闭条将在
smooth it when you're gluing always
回到他们找到自己的地方
所以如果你看它的结尾，你会看到
smooth it when you're gluing always
smear the glue right up to the crease so
两个插槽如何关闭
靠得越来越近
smear the glue right up to the crease so
there it is
这就是为什么不能超过三个
厘米宽，称为拉动
there it is
well that round to make it go smoothly
打开那里，现在我要戴上
第二张图片，这是背面
well that round to make it go smoothly
so that's how the main long piece looks
吧这不超过七个
厘米宽，让我们现在放一些胶水
so that's how the main long piece looks
so when it closes down it'll close like
在那一个可以下降到那里
只需将其关闭并向下按
so when it closes down it'll close like
this so now we have to add it to the
所以这就是整个事情了
您可能会感觉到的另一件事
this so now we have to add it to the
frame for that we have these two sleeves
他们实际上可以去的一侧滑动
在太远的地方，这有点
frame for that we have these two sleeves
so we've got these two sleeves they're
棘手的，所以你可以放一点卡
向下的每一侧都将充当
so we've got these two sleeves they're
the pieces that go at the back you can
州长，也不要阻止它
到目前为止，我只想简单地
the pieces that go at the back you can
see I haven't got them colored but
这样做，这应该是
这一半应该足够长
see I haven't got them colored but
there's a sleeve here and a sleeve here
认为如此，这些需要永远如此
略长于这些的宽度
there's a sleeve here and a sleeve here
they're the ones that hold these sliding
滑动件这样继续下去
把它剪下来，让你滑动
they're the ones that hold these sliding
pieces in place and make them move the
进入完全关闭的位置
然后在实际上放一些胶水
pieces in place and make them move the
way you want them to move so I've got
滑动片，我将滑动片放置
最多是您希望它是如此
way you want them to move so I've got
two of those they're just a fraction
那里是幻灯片的边缘
与框架边缘齐平
two of those they're just a fraction
longer than the whole height of the
然后我们将其粘在上面
靠在袖子上，所以它不会滑入
longer than the whole height of the
sliding piece so they are ten point five
任何进一步的推动，我都会
整理一下，就是那边
sliding piece so they are ten point five
centimeters and they're going to glue on
这样就可以了，我会在
另一侧，但滑盖是齐平的
centimeters and they're going to glue on
the back of this so I've got the
与框架的边缘，但一点点
一点胶在这里，然后粘贴
the back of this so I've got the
measurements here but I'll keep the
再次统治片段，我还没有削减
预先确定大小
measurements here but I'll keep the
measurements on the back I'm going to
使滑动件就位并
坚持这支统治
measurements on the back I'm going to
stick these on this they go right up
阻止它继续下去，所以我们
现在你可以看到像这样
stick these on this they go right up
flush against the window I put glue on
也许这些多余的东西看起来
有点笨重，所以你实际上
flush against the window I put glue on
the two tabs 1 2and these go like this
只是修剪他们只需要
长约半厘米
the two tabs 1 2and these go like this
ideally I would have measured it so that
比实际的滑动片
足以抵住袖子和
ideally I would have measured it so that
they're exactly equidistant above and
阻止它进行得太快，所以我会削减
那些都回来了哦，是的，所以
they're exactly equidistant above and
below the window frame so there's one is
这就是开始阶段设定的
一本书使他保持平整更长的时间
below the window frame so there's one is
the other one and just make sure that's
它的顶部或所有折痕
会加强，而且倾向于
the other one and just make sure that's
creased well as well but glue on those
保持自己的关闭方式
所以这是一个相当有趣的舞台
creased well as well but glue on those
two
将类型设置为
[音乐]
then be careful with this gluing you